asthebunnyhops.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy and Terms Of Use - As The Bunny Hops®

Please enjoy this page-turner of a Privacy Policy that hopefully keeps all of my advertisers, the FTC, random lawyers and the European Union totally happy. Please use As The Bunny Hops® at your own risk. Not responsible for glue gun burns, glitter in your eyes, burnt cupcakes or any other losses or injuries.

## Who we are

Our website address is https://asthebunnyhops.com, and it’s 99% (that’s just a guess, sometimes I ask for help) run by me. My name is and always has been Amy Fulcher, even if I say it’s Alexander Hamilton while singing in the shower. You’ll notice I use the word “we” a lot here. Consider it the royal “we”. If you need to contact me, send me an email at amy@asthebunnyhops.com.

## What Data Of Yours We Collect And What We Do With It

We’re trying to give YOU information, not take yours. But just like pretty much any other site, there are bits of your data that are collected when you visit. Most of this takes place with [web cookies](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie). At any time you can send in an email request and we’ll erase any personal data associated with your email address stored on this site.

## Advertising

As The Bunny Hops allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit this site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) or <http://www.youradchoices.com/>.

As The Bunny Hops is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com. As The Bunny Hops also contains other advertising and affiliate marketing links. A commission on sales of the products that are linked may be earned. There may also be affiliate links from third party websites. Cookies may be used to track these purchases.

So basically, this is my job and I make money from ads and commissions when you buy using my affiliate links. Sometimes little bits of data follow you around on the internet to help me do this.

## Comments

When you leave a comment on this site, we collect the data shown in the comments form. We also collect the IP address and browser to help detect spam comments.

The Gravatar service collects an anonymized string created from your email address which is then provided to their service to see if you are using it. This is what puts your cute little profile picture beside your comments. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/.  

## Embedded content from other websites

If we link or embed something here on this site  (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.) from other websites, it behaves in the exact same way as if you visited that other site.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Analytics

Google Analytics is used to provide us with visitor data and statistics. We don’t sell this data, but we sometimes aggregate it to sell us. “Look at how many cool people are visiting our site! You should totally hire us!” Read more about Google Analytics data practices here: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en

## Publishing Partners

Remember those ads I mentioned up above? Another way I make money is by creating sponsored content. Here are some of the companies I work with from time to time. Influencer marketing companies sometimes use tracking tools to monitor engagement with their sponsored content. You’ll always see a disclosure at the top of any post that is sponsored letting you know it’s advertising.

[  
  
](http://cbi.as/sofab)  
[  
](http://www.whoispollinate.com/)
